Guide to the Cookie Teer Papers, 1971-2000, bulk 1983-1997 RL.01282
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1971-2000, 37 boxes
  - Work in south statistics (Box 36)
  - Women's studies, 1983-1992 (3 folders) (Box 36, Box 36A)
  - Women's studies – women's history (Box 36)
  - Women's studies – women's history – women's strike (Box 36)
  - Various feminism articles (Box 36)
  - Women Writers Conference – Kentucky, 1988 (Box 36)
  - Wonderland – mail order child porn (Box 36)
  - Wright, Clara – Sanford, N.C. (Box 36)
  - Wynter, Sarah (Box 36)
  - Yale Law/ Feminism (Box 37)
  - Yager, Fay (Box 37)
  - Zilber, Suzanne (Box 37)
  - Zillman, Dolf (Box 37)
  - Zillman correspondence, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Zillman – "Effects of Exposure" (Box 37)
  - Zillman – callousness (Box 37)
  - Zillman letter (Box 37)
  - Zillman, Dolf – "Effects of Prolonged Consumption of Porno" (Box 37)
  - Odd (Box 37)
  - P.A. stat – camera ready (Box 37)
  - Stencils (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous – Orange County Rape Crisis Center (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous printed materials (Box 37)
  - Playboar, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous – custody (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous – Endometriosis Data Project introductory packets (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous – pamphlets – Endometriosis Association, OCRCC, PSST… (Box 37)
  - Orange County Human Relations Commission – Michelle Zilk – testimony re: disability/ gender-based discrimination (endometriosis), 1989 Sept. 20 (Box 37)
- Orange County Human Relations Commission Series, 1985-1992, 5 boxes
  This series contains materials related to the Orange County Human Relations Commission as well as the Committee for Justice for Women of Orange County, both of which are part of the Orange County Office of Human Rights and Relations. Teer was a member of the Orange County Human Relations Commission from 1988 to 1992, and co-founded the Committee for Justice for Women in 1989. Some materials consist of pamphlets or news clippings related to the HRC's focus areas, especially the status of women and children within the county and the state. This series also contains planning for and documentation of the public hearings on the status of women and children in Orange County, N.C., organized by the Human Relations Commission and held in 1989.
  - Hearings on the quality of life and civil rights status of women and children, 1989 Oct. 9-10 and 16-17 (Box 38)
  - Committee for Justice for Women in Orange County – vigil, Dawn Jolly (Box 38)
  - Women's symposium (Box 38)
  - Incest law in N.C. (Box 38)
  - Ordinance, 1988 (Box 38)
  - Judge Friday, The Cave rape case, 1989 Aug. (Box 38)
  - Organization, 1989 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 38)
  - Articles, news clippings, statistics about women and children, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Public hearings press information guide, 1989 Oct. (Box 38)
  - Public hearings press release, 1989 Oct. 9 (Box 38)
  - Women and children articles – copy order (Box 38)
  - Public hearings – articles about women and children (Box 38)
  - Public hearings speakers, 1989 (Box 38)
  - Planning notes for public hearings, 1989, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Public hearings on women and children, 1989 Oct. 9-17 (Box 38)
  - Public hearing report, 1990 Feb. 1 (Box 38)
  - Public hearings – drafts of testimony transcripts (Box 39)
  - Public hearings on women and children – Cookie Teer, 1989 Oct. (Box 39)
  - Public hearings on women and children – 1989 Oct. 9 (Box 39)
  - Public hearings on women and children – 1989 Oct. 10 (Box 39)
  - Public hearings on women and children – 1989 Oct. 16, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Public hearings on women and children – 1989 Oct. 17, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Bylaws, meeting minutes (Box 39)
  - Minneapolis civil rights ordinance – city codes, 1985 and 1987 (Box 39)
  - Mothers/ children/ custody (Box 39)
  - Child sex abuse (Box 40)
  - NOW/ LDF child sex abuse briefs, 1989 (Box 40)
  - MA civil rights laws, 1990 (Box 40)
  - WI civil rights laws, 1990 (Box 40)
  - Minneapolis, MN civil rights ordinance, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Santa Cruz, CA – domestic partnership, 1989 (Box 40)
  - IL – civil liability (Box 40)
  - University of MI – "policy" decision (Box 40)
  - Hate crimes bill, 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Human Relations Commission main file (Box 40)
  - HRC ordinance references (Box 40)
  - Minneapolis civil rights ordinance, 1985 and 1987 (Box 40)
  - North Carolina civil rights (Box 40)
  - Orange County Health Department community diagnosis, 1990 Feb. (Box 40)
  - Public hearings recommendations, Human Rights Office proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 40)
  - HRC news clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Memos, meeting minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Public hearing report – homophobia (Box 40)
  - Public hearing report – racism (Box 40)
  - Public hearing report – employment (Box 40)
  - Public hearing report – quality of life and civil rights status of women and children, 1 Feb. 1990 (Box 40)
  - Notebook (Box 40)
  - Articles about issues, 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Meeting notes, memos, 1991-1992 (Box 41)
  - Civil rights ordinance notes, draft, comments (Box 41)
  - CJW custody report, 1991 June 6 (Box 41)
  - Old town/ county/ state officials mailing lists (Box 41)
  - Committee for Justice for Women – child custody articles, workshop, 1991 (Box 41)
  - Orange County civil rights ordinance, 1991 Mar.-Apr. (Box 41)
  - Committee for Justice for Women – custody – Kathy Crook (Box 41)
  - Therese Stanton – "Tomorrow I'll Miss You" (Box 41)
  - Village Books v. City of Bellingham, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Child custody – Marianne Mickey Norman v. State of N.C. (Box 41)
  - Books about incest (Box 41)
  - General statutes of North Carolina – domestic violence, 1989 Nov. 1 (Box 41)
  - Orange County civil rights ordinance draft, 1991 Feb. 20 (Box 41)
  - IOF Foresters Against Child Abuse – brochures, small print (Box 41)
  - Committee for Children videos and lessons (Box 41)
  - National Children's Advocacy Center (Box 41)
  - Parents Anonymous – Delaware Committee for Prevention of Child Abuse (Box 41)
  - National Committee for Prevention of Child Abuse (Box 41)
  - Kids Rights, 1991 Winter-Spring (Box 41)
  - Orange County power mapping (Box 41)
  - Pornography Awareness mailing list (Box 41)
  - Contact info, mailing lists (Box 41)
  - NC laws – custody, divorce (Box 41)
  - Attorney General's Commission on Pornography – public hearing transcript, 1985 Sept. 11 (Box 41)
  - Ntozake Shange (Box 41)
  - Male supremacist sexuality packet (Box 41)
  - Pornography packet (Box 41)
  - Child sexual abuse packet (Box 41)
  - Rape and prostitution packet (Box 42)
  - Informational packets (Box 42)
  - Informational packets originals (Box 42)
  - Undated letter – informational packets (Box 42)
- Attorney General's Commission on Pornography Series, 1983-1986, 5 boxes
  The Attorney General's Commission on Pornography Series contains materials related to the commission's 1985-1986 investigation into pornography, which resulted in the Meese Report. Consisting almost entirely of transcripts from public hearings on pornography, some with annotations, this series details many aspects of the U.S. pornography industry. This series also contains some materials from the 1983 Minneapolis hearings on pornography, which were part of a movement to create a city-wide Anti-pornography Civil Rights Ordinance.
  - Public hearing, Los Angeles, 1985 Oct. 17, 3 folders (Box 43)
  - Public hearing, Miami, 1985 Nov. 20, 3 folders (Box 43)
  - Report of the Attorney General's Commission on Pornography, 1986 Apr. 28, 1-3 of 6 folders (Box 43)
  - Report of the Attorney General's Commission on Pornography, 1986 Apr. 28, 4-6 of 6 folders (Box 44)
  - Public hearing, Houston, 1985 Sept. 11, 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Public hearing, Houston, 1985 Sept. 12, 1 of 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Public hearing, Houston, 1985 Sept. 12, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Minneapolis hearings on pornography, annotated, 1983 Dec. 12, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Minneapolis hearings on pornography, clean copy, 1983 Dec. 12, 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Public hearing, Washington, DC, 1985 June 19, 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Pornography Awareness pins and business cards (Box 45)
  - Public hearing, New York, 1986 Jan. 21, 5 folders (Box 46)
  - Public hearing, New York, 1986 Jan. 22, 5 folders (Box 46)
  - Public hearing, Chicago, 1985 July 24, 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Public hearing, Chicago, 1985 July 25, 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Public hearing, Los Angeles, 1985 Oct. 16, 4 folders (Box 47)
- Southern Sisters Bookstore Series, 1984-1995, 6 boxes
  The Southern Sisters Bookstore Series contains materials related to the feminist/women's Southern Sisters Bookstore, of which Teer was co-owner, President, and CEO. Located at 411 Morris Street in Durham, N.C., the bookstore was founded in 1988, and closed in 1995. Materials include financial records, flyers, mailing lists, mission statement, bibliographies of materials related to feminist issues, as well as materials such as cards from the bookstore's Rolodex, signs, and rubber stamps. Contains some correspondence from patrons, donors, and supporters of the store.
  Boxes 50 and 51 contain business cards and Rolodex entries.
  - Duke Intro to Women's Studies course pack, 1984 Fall (Box 48)
  - Recommended titles by subject (Box 48)
  - Southern Sisters message notebook, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Abuse bibliography/ catalog mail orders completed, 1994 May-Oct. (Box 48)
  - Southern Sisters – miscellaneous blank forms (Box 48)
  - Worst seller list, 1988 Aug. – 1989 Aug. (Box 48)
  - Staff daily logs, 1991 (Box 48)
  - Computer inventory files memo (Box 48)
  - Allison's notebook/ store manual (Box 48)
  - S.O. mail orders completed, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Porn and C.R. – paid receipts (Box 48)
  - Porn and C.R. orders (Box 48)
  - Orders/ Porn and Civil Rights flyers (Box 48)
  - Porn and C.R. returns (Box 48)
  - Abuse/ mail order catalog completed order, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Mail order, bibliography correspondence, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Violence/ abuse mailing list/ correspondence (Box 48)
  - Book photos (Box 48)
  - Southern Sisters schedules, notes, 1994 (Box 49)
  - Data – Bib. Sales (Box 49)
  - FBN mail order/ catalog (Box 49)
  - Marketing, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Side Lines inventory (Box 49)
  - Monthly sales tax reports, blank (Box 49)
  - Mail and phone order log, 1994-1995 (Box 49)
  - Robbery – 1991 May-June (Box 49)
  - Break-ins, 1994 (Box 49)
  - Robberies, 1993 (Box 49)
  - Store info, 1994 (Box 49)
  - Annual store business meeting, 1989 Aug. 2 (Box 49)
  - Small business loan program (Box 49)
  - Goals of store (Box 49)
  - Privilege licenses N.C. (Box 49)
  - Wholesale license – copies (Box 49)
  - Southern Sisters archive, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Southern Sisters archive – newspaper clippings (Box 49)
  - Southern Sisters archive – store manual (Box 49)
  - Art events – invitations, etc. (Box 49)
  - Literary events and storytelling – past (Box 49)
  - Woman money (progressive shopping day), 1991 Dec. 7-8 (Box 49)
  - Where in the World is Southern Sisters? Map (Box 49)
  - Southern Sisters newsletter and birthday card, 1994 (Box 49)
  - FBN catalogue, 1994 Fall (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters matron flyer, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters bookmark by Bibba, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters postcard/ Cayman's drawing, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Newsletter, 1994 Dec. (Box 50)
  - Ads, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters brochure (to be sent to schools, etc.) (Box 50)
  - Cut and paste for ads, hours and address (Box 50)
  - Independent Bookstore Network (Box 50)
  - Women's Declaration of Independence (Box 50)
  - My head is full brochure (Box 50)
  - Old flyers – originals (Box 50)
  - Ad and flyer originals (Box 50)
  - Cassettes – mothers who lost their children by Judge Peele, Southern Sisters on 103.9, 1993 Apr. 13 (Box 50)
  - Calendar images (Box 50)
  - Advertisement copies (Box 50)
  - Matron bags (Box 50)
  - Matron list, 1994 Dec. (Box 50)
  - School and organization mailing list; flyer, PSA, and newspaper labels (Box 50)
  - Calendar dates (Box 50)
  - Progressive shopping, 1990-1991 (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters calendars, 1993-1994 (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters letterhead (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters mailing lists (Box 50)
  - Order forms, 1994-1995 (Box 50)
  - Abuse bibliography, sales analysis (Box 50)
  - Bibliography, 1994 Nov. 17 (Box 50)
  - Child abuse resources, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Original abuse bibliography (Box 50)
  - Resources for Survivors and Professionals, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Screened PMTs, grassroots printing, 1994 (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters resources catalog – order and bibliography (Box 50)
  - Violence/abuse catalog update (Box 50)
  - Violence/abuse catalog mailing list (Box 50)
  - Violence/abuse catalog original (Box 50)
  - Calendars (Box 50)
  - Southern Sisters rolodex (Box 51)
  - Rubber stamps (Box 51)
  - Southern Sisters stickers (Box 51)
  - Subject file index (Box 52)
  - Store accounts (Box 52)
  - Matrons (Box 52)
  - Rolodex – Southern Sisters (Box 52)
  - Store signs (Box 53)
- Oversized Materials, 1984-1996, 3 boxes
  - box 54, 1986-1995 (Box 54, 1986-1995)
  - Calendar (Box 54, 1986-1995)
  - Sexual Harrassment (Box 54, 1986-1995)
  - Southern Sisters Bookstore (Box 54, 1986-1995)
  - box 55, 1984-1996 (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Sexual Liberals and the Attack on Feminism (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Linea Smith (Playboy) (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Snuff (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Symposiums (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - NCCU Symposium (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Take Back the Night (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Bronwyn Boraky (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Toronto Symposium (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Pat Turlington (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - University of North Carolina Women's Studies (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - Vodas, M. (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - WAP Conference, April 1986 (Box 55, 1984-1996)
  - box 56, 1987-1995 (Box 56, 1987-1995)
  - WAS (Box 56, 1987-1995)
  - Women Honored (Box 56, 1987-1995)
  - Women in Prison (Box 56, 1987-1995)
  - Women, Work, and Education (Box 56, 1987-1995)
  - Women's Review of Books (Box 56, 1987-1995)
  - P.A. Stat (Box 56, 1987-1995)
  - Marketing (Box 56, 1987-1995)